Guide to the Darinka Archive, 1973-2010 MSS.340
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Audio Recordings
  - Subseries B: Darinka Music
    - The Rage of 1710's, undated; ID: 340.0147 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0147)
    - Roxy Music, undated; ID: 340.0148 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0148)
    - Roxy Music, "Flesh and Blood," Bowie, "Ashes to Ashes", undated; ID: 340.0149 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0149)
    - Sakamoto; James Brown, undated; ID: 340.0150 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0150)
    - Satie: Parade, undated; ID: 340.0151 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0151)
    - Thomas Schippers Conducts Samuel Barber, undated; ID: 340.0152 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0152)
    - Simple Minds, undated; ID: 340.0153 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0153)
    - Ska, undated; ID: 340.0154 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0154)
    - Stargazers, undated; ID: 340.0155 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0155)
    - TOTB - Theory of Total Blame - Las Vegas, undated; ID; 340.0156 (Box 9, Media ID; 340.0156)
    - Tears, undated; ID: 340.0157 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0157)
    - Debussy: Prelude al'apres-midi d'un faune, Undated; cuid22001 (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0158)
    - U.N.C.L.E. - Soundtrack, undated; ID: 340.0159 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0159)
    - Via Afrika, undated; ID: 340.0160 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0160)
    - Village Music of Bulgaria, undated; ID: 340.0161 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0161)
    - Steve Winwood, "Chronicles", undated; ID: 340.0162 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0162)
    - Yellow Magic Orchestra, undated; ID: 340.0163 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0163)
    - Yello - Elvis - Devo, undated; ID: 340.0164 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0164)
    - Yello and Devo, undated; ID: 340.0165 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0165)
  - Subseries C: Demos and Miscellaneous
    This subseries contains various demo tapes and unidentified material.
    - The Actuals, undated; ID: 340.0166 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0166)
    - Alien Planetscapes, "Skylore", undated; ID: 340.0167 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0167)
    - Green Night Audio Leter, undated; ID: 340.0168 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0168)
    - Jole Blonde, undated; ID: 340.0169 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0169)
    - Jenny Bruce, "Demo Tape", undated; ID: 340.0170 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0170)
    - Bump, undated; ID: 340.0171 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0171)
    - Doomster, "Refreshes While You Smoke", undated; ID: 340.0172 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0172)
    - Howard #1, undated; ID: 340.0173 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0173)
    - Loser's Preshow Song, undated; ID: 340.0174 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0174)
    - Loser's Preshow Music (Matter of Time), undated; ID: 340.0175 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0175)
    - Nirvana, "Nevermind", undated; ID: 340.0176 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0176)
    - Martland Peters 1 & 2, undated; ID: 340.0177 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0177)
    - David Algeo Smith, "Demo", undated; ID: 340.0178 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0178)
    - Stephan Smith, "The Ballad of Abner Louima", undated; ID: 340.0179 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0179)
    - Jeff & Gary 3 Song Demo, undated; ID: 340.0180 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0180)
    - Tellus: The Audio Cassette Magazine #10, undated; ID: 340.0181 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0181)
    - Tellus: The Audio Cassette Magazine #20, undated; ID: 340.0182 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0182)
    - Unfinished Journey, undated; ID: 340.0183 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0183)
    - Wedding Ceremony, undated; ID: 340.0184 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0184)
    - Luxury Knives Demo Tape, undated; ID: 340.0185 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0185)
    - Luxury Knives Demo Tape, undated; ID: 340.0186 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0186)
    - Luxury Knives Demo Tape, undated; ID: 340.0187 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0187)
    - Early Recording, undated; ID: 340.0188 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0188)
    - Don't Do Me Any Favors Pre-Show & House, undated; ID: 340.0189 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0189)
    - Unknown, undated; ID: 340.0190 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0190)
    - Unknown, undated; ID: 340.0191 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0191)
    - Unknown, undated; ID: 340.0192 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0192)
    - Unknown, undated; ID: 340.0193 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0193)
    - Jousd #5, undated; ID: 340.0194 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0194)
    - Other Side Jam w/Rob - Guitar; Chuck - Drum, undated; ID: 340.0195 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0195)
    - Unknown, undated; ID: 340.0196 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0196)
    - Gemini cassette head cleaner, undated; ID: 340.0197 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0197)
    - Audio cassette head cleaner, undated; ID: 340.0198 (Box 9, Media ID: 340.0198)
  - Subseries D: Additional Sound Recordings
    Open to researchers. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival collections.
    Audiovisual materials in Subseries D are commmercially released material and are available to researchers.
    - After the Fall #12, undated; ID: N/A (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
      Original format: Sound Disc: Digital; 4 3/4 in.
    - Below Houston #4, undated; ID: N/A (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
    - Black and White World #1, undated; ID: N/A (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
    - Black and White World #3, undated; ID: N/A (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
    - RobK ExCorpse, undated; ID: N/A (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
    - Workdogs In Hell, 1992; ID: N/A (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
    - Workdogs Old, 1994; ID: N/A (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
    - Al Jolson: Al Jolson Souvenir Album, 1953; ID: N/A (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
      General
      Contains handwritten annotation: "G Ray keep up the good work [Crocker]"
      Original format: 7" EP Vinyl Sound Disc; 45rpm
    - Machine & Hummer, "Introvert" 1. "room beyond the door" 2. "angel in rags", undated; ID: N/A (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
    - Squeegies, 1. "Don't Tread on Flowers" 2. "I Wanna Know Right Now", 1967; ID: N/A (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
    - Gary, Quazar, 1. "Suicide 2. Lesbian Boy; News, undated; ID: N/A (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
      Contains handwritten annotation: "Hey Gary, [Gary] Quazar"
    - Workdogs, 1. "Funny $" 2. "Last Friend's Gone", 1986; ID: N/A (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
      Original format: 7" EP Vinyl Sound Disc; 33 1/3 rpm
    - Finis Coronat Opus (23) - A Jim Sharp Product, 1990; ID: N/A (Box 11, Media ID: N/A)
      Contains handwritten annotation: "To Gary - Here's Comin' at Ya --- Jim S -- 12-15-90 1:45 AM Brooklyn"
      Plastikville Records. Side B is blank
      Original format: 7" EP Vinyl Sound Disc; 46rpm
- Series IV: Video Recordings
  This series contains video recordings of performances at Darinka.
  - Twad Schuetrum, 1985 November 1; ID: 340.0216 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0216)
    Original format: VHS
  - Richard Kern, "Manhattan Love Suicides", 1985; ID: 340.0206 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0206)
  - Kimberly Flynn at Darinka, 1986 September 19; ID: 340.0217 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0217)
  - Avant Garde Arama with Kimberly Flynn, 1986 October 17; ID: 340.0218 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0218)
  - Gary Ray: It Comes In Waves (Rough Edit), 1986; 340.0202 (Box 10, Cassette 340.0202)
    Format: VHS, Duration: 88 min.
  - The Agaloff Sisters at La Mama (with Kimberly Flynn), 1987 November 14; ID: 340.0219 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0219)
  - "The Doorman", 1987; ID: 340.0205 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0205)
  - Jason Brandenburg, "Moonglow", 1987; ID: 340.0208 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0208)
  - Jason Brandenburg, "Moonglow", 1987; ID: 340.0207 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0207)
  - Blind Double Date, 1989; ID: 340.0201 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0201)
  - Theory of Total Blame, Rapp Art Center NYC: Karen Finley, 1989 June 18; ID: 340.0215 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0215)
  - Church of the Little Green Man at Max Fish, 1990 October; 340.0203 (Box 10, Cassette 340.0203)
    Original format: VHS, Duration: 57 min.
  - Czolgosz at PS122, 1990; ID: 340.0204 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0204)
    Orginal format: VHS
  - Gary Ray: Organic Extensionism, 1992 May 16; ID: 340.0209 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0209)
  - Biohazardous, 2001; ID: 340.0200 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0200)
  - Gary Ray hosting AGA, 2003; ID: 340.0199 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0199)
  - "A Slice of Life," William Kent, undated; ID: 340.0213 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0213)
  - Chett Grant: A Portrait of the Man, undated; ID: 340.0212 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0212)
  - "Poison" (Rough Cut), undated; ID: 340.0210 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0210)
  - "Poltergash", undated; ID: 340.0211 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0211)
  - Milestone Film, "Spread the Word", undated; ID: 340.0214 (Box 10, Media ID: 340.0214)
- Series V: Data Storage
  This series contains files and photographs, stored on computer disks.
  - Darinka - Misc. photos - NYC-LES-Performance, 1970's, 1980's, 1990's, Undated; cuid22002 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0001)
    Format: DVD-R
  - Darinka Bak - ML - World and USA File, Undated; cuid22003 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0002)
    Format: 5 1/4" DSDD Computer Disk
  - Darinka ML, Undated; cuid22004 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0003)
  - List, Undated; cuid22005 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0004)
  - Worldstar disk 6 - Advanced features, Mail list, Undated; cuid22006 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0005)
  - Copyiipc, Undated; cuid22007 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0006)
  - SOS Backup Dsk, 2-16-94, 20 pages, circa 1994; cuid22008 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0007)
  - Play - early SOS, Undated; cuid22009 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0008)
  - Conn Bak-up - Saved, Undated; cuid22010 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0009)
  - Data on-file castbox, Undated; cuid22011 (Box 10, Disk ID: 340.3.0010)
- Series VI: Photographs
  - Photo album (black cover), Undated; cuid22012 (Box 16)
  - Photo album (red cover), Undated; cuid22013 (Box 12)
  - Lenticular photograph: Ethyl Eichelberger performing at Darinka, 1986; cuid22014 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Lenticular photograph: Washington Square Park, circa 1985; cuid22015 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Lenticular photograph: Larry Steger and Emily Sherman Marynczak at Darinka, circa 1984; cuid22016 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Series VII. 2015 Accretion
  - Invitations, 1985-1991; cuid22017 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Soho, 1991-1992; cuid22018 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Stop, 1990-1991; cuid22019 (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
- Oversize Series I: Darinka Files
  This series contains the oversize material separated from series I, including posters and magazine clippings.
  - "Adam Bomb" lyric poster, Undated; cuid22020 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Carlo McCormick benefit poster, Undated; cuid22021 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Darinka stencils by Paul Chelstad, Undated; cuid22022 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - East Village Eye - blurb, 1984 September; cuid22023 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ethyl Eichelberger / Karen Finley poster, Undated; cuid22024 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Factory / Market poster, Undated; cuid22025 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Gigantic - movie poster, Undated; cuid22026 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Head to the Future poster, Undated; cuid22027 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Issue of "Backstage", 1985 June 28; cuid22028 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Johanna Went poster and press release, 1985 June 9; cuid22029 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Mike Osterhout "M" poster, Undated; cuid22030 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Misc. news articles, 1985, 1987; cuid22031 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - "The New Common Good" article, Undated; cuid22032 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - New Ice Nights poster, 1986; cuid22033 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - New York Newsday "City Living", 1991 April 4; cuid22034 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1987-1989; cuid22035 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Nick Zedd's "School of Shame" poster, Undated; cuid22036 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Nick Zedd / B. Moran / R. Kern poster, 1984; cuid22037 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Observe poster, Undated; cuid22038 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Paper magazine, 1986; cuid22039 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Soul Samurai poster, 2009; cuid22040 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Stop Rock Movie poster, undated; cuid22047 (Folder 15)
  - These Showers Can Talk poster, Undated; cuid22041 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - "Tubby Boots" poster, Undated; cuid22042 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Village Voice - "East Side Confidential", 1984 November 13; cuid22043 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Theory of Total Blame poster, 1988; cuid22044 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Village Voice - "Kitchen" article, 1985 March 5; cuid22045 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - "When Lithuania Ruled the World part III" poster, Undated; cuid22046 (Box 3, Folder 22)